[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
That's Ma'am Pia's report.
Mandatory leadership and
operational compliance training.
Possible suspension.
If that man wasn't involved
in your operation
the report would be different.
Where did you take
the motorcycle?
There was a mishap
so I had to leave it.
The money he'll pay is
for your dad's medical expenses!
You failed!
Now the money's gone!
Don't worry. I'll get it back.
We can't just walk in
through there.
We'll go through the back.
The man who messed up
our operation.
I believe that guy is the key
for us to solve
this gold smuggling case.
Get every piece of information
linked to that motorcycle.
It will lead the way
for me to find him.
I need to get
the motorcycle back.
Look carefully. Let's split up.
[ARNEL] Miss KC,
what was it [SIGHS]
that you want to talk about?
It's about Salvador.
Miss KC,
I did everything I could.
I squeezed him dry
just to improve his reports!
It did improve!
The ratings increased.
The public is very invested.
Salvador's report is a hit!
You're welcome, Ma'am!
It was me who really brought out
the best in Salvador!
I'll have you know,
it was thanks to me, ma'am!
We will capitalize
on this, Arnel.
- It's time
- Yes, ma'am.
for us to really sell Salvador
out here.
- Yes, ma'am.
- We'll give Salvador a show
where he will be
the host himself.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Oli.
I went home
while the commander's mad.
[CLATTERING]
- [SIGHS]
- [DOOR OPENS]
Salvador! Salvador!
[PANTING]
Get rid of those
reporter clothes!
You are going to be a host!
Hose? Like a garden hose?
No, Salvador!
- You will have your own show!
- Show...
And you are the star!
Even if you don't look like one!
Even if you don't
look like a star,
your name will be known
by the entire country
as Salvador Manalo.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, you're amazing!
[STUTTERING] Congratulations!
You did so well!
- Boss, hold on.
- Yeah?
Boss, get this.
Once I strike it big,
I promise you,
I won't forget about you.
You know what, we just need
to do a makeover.
N-- not too much makeover,
I hope.
Don't stray too far
from how people knew me
they might just get confused.
Did you become popular?
You didn't, right?
That's why we'll change it
and give you a cooler image!
I mean, you do look brave
despite your short height
and dark skin.
But don't worry.
We'll gradually change you,
starting from the way you dress.
You made the most of it,
didn't you, boss?
You mixed insults
with your compliments.
You just have to look like
the enemy of wicked men!
You'll fight
against all the criminals!
All of them
will be scared of you!
What if this kills me?
That is part of the job.
[DOOR OPENS, SHUTS]
I'm just trying
to understand her.
Her mind's still clouded.
[RALLOS] Sir, now is when
she needs you most.
You have to make an effort now.
Timing is everything.
The only thing
I can tell you now, Sir Seb...
...is don't lose hope
because to me,
you are still the one.
I won't approach her for now,
while her mind's still clouded.
[RALLOS] But, sir,
you can make an effort
without annoying her.
What do you mean?
- Have you spoken to Ma'am Pia?
- That's right, sir.
Ma'am Pia might change
her assessment of our case.
[RALLOS] And if you do that
great favor for Ma'am Sam,
she'll appreciate you even more!
You'll be the star, sir.
[KAREN] And she'll fall in love
with you
because you are the answer
to her problems.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
[HANDS CLAP]
[PAPERS RUSTLE]
[SEBASTIAN CLEARS THROAT]
Ma'am Pia.
[PIA CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Ma'am Pia?
[PIA CLEARS THROAT]
Call me Pia.
It's just us here, anyway.
[SEBASTIAN CLEARS THROAT]
I'd rather call you Ma'am Pia.
So, ma'am, uh...
Regarding your assessment
of Sam.
I believe your assessment
of her performance
was inaccurate.
Why are you...
...so concerned about her?
[DOOR SLIDING]
Didn't you like...
...the good review
I gave you?
No, no, no, ma'am.
I am truly grateful,
and I thank you.
And you're grateful.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm...
You know, Sebastian...
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
You won't gain anything
from Jacinto.
The top of the NCIA ladder...
...is too high.
You should be smart
in choosing your connections,
so you can climb
that ladder quickly.
[SEBASTIAN SCOFFS]
You know, ma'am,
I didn't really dream of--
Shh!
[PIA TUTTING]
Shh...
Everyone wants to reach
the top.
I'm already on top.
Believe me, Sebastian.
It's great up here.
It's very, very great.
I can do a lot of things
for you.
[PIA INHALES SHARPLY]
Just say the word.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[DOOR SLIDING]
[STEALTHY MUSIC PLAYING]
Tolits, there are
so many cars here.
Some are even rotting!
Seems like you fit in here.
You're rotting too.
- Huh? Why me?
- Shush!
You're too noisy,
don't be noisy!
The next time we go here,
we'll rob a nice car,
so we look handsome
when we go out!
[DABOY] I'd love to have
a Beetle.
- That car suits me just fine!
- A Beetle?
How will you even fit there
with that belly?
- Shush, shush, shush!
- Hold me back!
- Don't be loud!
- You're loud!
- There's someone!
- Hey!
[BINOY] There's someone!
Let's hide here, c'mon!
[STEALTHY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TEKLA] Gabo!
Why did you have to mess
with the motorbike
Sir Rudy's fixing?
Now you're in a mess!
[GABO SIGHS]
I didn't know. I just want him
to get his surgery.
That's why I took it.
I get it,
but now it's a mess!
What are we going to do now?
Miss Betchay is so mad at you.
Mama Betchay's
always been like that.
Even when I was a kid...
She was often mad at me.
[GLOOMY MUSIC PLAYING]
- Do you see those guys?
- [EXHALES]
Tekla.
Use your beauty and charm.
Act like you have questions
for them.
Find out where the
motor parts are located,
then ask where they store
the motorcycles.
[GLOOMY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'm your girl.
You can count on me, Gabo.
I'll play my beauty
and charm card.
- Okay.
- I've got this.
Be careful.
[QUIRKY TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BONG] Someone's coming!
- [DABOY] Hurry!
- Come on!
- Over there!
- Down here!
- Move it!
- Get down!
- [BINOY] Ouch!
Shush!
[TOLITS WHISPERS]
Don't make a sound!
[THUDS]
- [PEE TRICKLING]
- [QUIRKY TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ZIPPER RASPS]
Come on, keep going!
Boys, follow me!
- Help me!
- [GROANS]
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
[TOLITS, BINOY GRUNT]
Come on!
[FLIRTY MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAN 1] Hey, guys.
The motorcycle delivered
last night was stunning.
Do you think they'll pick it up?
- [MAN 2] Not a chance.
- [MAN 3] Probably not.
[MAN 1] I hope not, so we can
dismantle it for parts.
[MAN 4] Bro, that woman is hot.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
- Hey, boys.
- [MAN 2] Miss...
How can we help you?
[FLIRTY MUSIC CONTINUES]
I was hoping to ask
if you sell parts here.
[MAN 1] Miss, what kind
of parts are you looking for?
For motorcycles,
if you have them here.
- Plenty, in fact.
- My big bike crashed.
When I brought it
to the repair shop,
the charge was pretty expensive.
Maybe you've got the parts here.
[MAN 2]
We definitely have them here.
They might be pricey, though.
Please don't charge
me too much.
[MAN 3] Well, that depends.
We can talk about it.
[GIGGLES]
[MAN 1] Miss...
Are you with someone?
Oh. Why?
Do you see someone
I don't, mister?
No! I came here on my own.
I worked up the courage,
hoping maybe you've got
cheaper parts.
Good thing you do.
Where are they?
Let's discuss it in our office.
Sure thing.
Where's your office?
- [MAN 3] Come on, join us.
- This way?
[MUSIC BECOMES THRILLING]
[SIGHS]
[TEASPON CLINKING]
[CHAIR RATTLES]
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
[ERNESTO CLEARS THROAT]
Sir, have you talked
to Ma'am Pia?
Mm-hmm.
I tried.
So, sir, why do you seem
more troubled?
[SEBASTIAN] I could tell...
she didn't want to talk
about Sam.
Bad timing, maybe.
But I'll take it slow with her.
[LIGHT MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
For Sam.
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOSS]
All you do is talk endlessly!
- Hide now!
- They're heading this way!
Hurry up!
[BOSS] You keep wasting time!
Why is that car door open?
I've warned you before!
[CAR DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Argh...
Shush, shush! Get out!
Come on, let's go!
[WORKER 1] Perfect timing.
There's a brand-new motorcycle.
- Really?
- Yes!
- What color?
- Miss, it's black!
And guess what?
It was delivered last night!
- It's stunning!
- Oh! That sounds like heaven!
- My motorcycle is also black!
- Then it's a match!
Could you show it to me?
Lead the way, please!
We'll give it to you for free.
Oh, that's too much!
Is it really free?
- Absolutely!
- Yeah!
So you won't have to spend
too much! Right, boys?
Hey, wait a minute! Hang on!
What if I can't give
what you want in return?
- Of course you can!
- You can do it!
[EXCITING MUSIC PLAYING]
[THUDDING]
[WORKER 2] We'll go over
the details in the office.
- Right, boys?
- Yeah, right!
[TEKLA] Okay, where is it?
[EXCITING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TEKLA] Don't scam me, okay?
[THUDDING]
[CAR DOOR RATTLES]
[TEKLA] Feels like you're
trying to rip me off!
[METAL PARTS CLANK]
[AIR WHOOSHING]
[SOFT THUD]
[TEKLA] Wow, I got lucky
meeting you boys today.
Now, I won't have to spend big
to get my motorcycle fixed.
[WORKER 3] You won't have
to spend a thing!
Because we're giving it to you!
[TEKLA GASPS] Seriously?!
- That's right!
- Just be a good girl...
and we'll give you
whatever you want.
[TEKLA] Oh, alright then!
So where's the motorcycle?
Where is it? That one?
B-But it's all busted up!
[WORKER 2] Not that one, miss.
That one!
- Where?
- Over there! Come on!
- That one?
- Yeah!
Take a look!
- Stunning, right?
- Wow!
- What a motorcycle!
- It's yours now!
- So handsome!
- Right?
- Look!
- It's stunning!
- It really is!
- Yeah!
If you want, you can have it.
- Exactly!
- Are you sure?
Here's the key.
- [HIGH FIVE]
- [GIGGLES]
- Can I fire it up?
- Of course!
- Go on!
- Oh my!
- Perfect!
- [HANDS CLAP]
[EXCITING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEY TURNS]
[EXHALES SOFTLY]
[ENGINE STARTS]
- Oh my!
- [WORKER 2] Hear that?
[TEKLA] It's just perfect! Wow!
It's better than my old bike!
The sound is awesome!
- It suits me, right?
- Absolutely!
We'll give you everything
you want here.
Just make sure...
you give us what we want
from you.
- Right, boys?
- Oh, yes!
- Well, of course!
- There we go!
So it's settled.
This is mine now.
[WORKER 2] Come on, miss.
Join us at the office.
We'll fix the release papers
so you can bring
your motorcycle home!
- Right, boys?
- Totally!
Wow, you're all so kind!
- Come on, let's go!
- This way, miss!
- Hurry up, boys!
- Follow us!
It's just over here!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KEY TURNS]
[ENGINE RUMBLING]
[ENGINE ROARING, REVVING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Are we sure
the motorcycle is here?
Maybe we're just looking
for nothing.
We're just going around
in circles.
I'm so tired.
Tolits, I'm hungry.
Talking won't help us find it.
It's here somewhere.
If it's really here,
then where is it?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[ENGINE REVVING]
Where the hell is your office?
We've been walking forever.
Are you guys screwing with me?
Miss, the office
is just up ahead.
- Right here?
- So we can fix
your motorcycle's
release papers.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
You better keep
your word, guys.
- Of course, it's just--
- Get it transferred to my name.
- This way.
- Here?
The office is right around
the back, miss.
- In the back?!
- Yes!
An office back there?
Is that even allowed?
That's where we always
process the papers.
- Alright, fine.
- It's much faster.
It's just right around here.
Just make sure my bike
gets released fast, okay?
Look, a dog!
[MAKING PSSTING SOUNDS]
Look how cute it is.
[GIGGLES]
It definitely got impounded,
since it's here.
Maybe its registration expired.
Registration?
Registration? It's a dog,
its owner just left it.
[DOGS GROWLING]
Once we find the bike,
we're taking this dog home.
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [DOGS BARKING]
- [DOGS SNARLING]
- Oh...
- [MOUTHING WORDS] One, two...
- Don't move.
If we move,
they'll maul us.
My grandpa said never run
from a dog.
Try smiling
so they get good vibes.
No?
[DOGS GROWLING, BARKING]
[WHIMPERS]
Don't worry, I know dogs,
I'm an animal lover.
- Go on then, try it.
- Okay.
- Just stay quiet.
- [PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MAKING PSSTING SOUNDS]
- You're calling them wrong!
- [BINOY WHIMPERS]
You're making cat sounds.
They're dogs,
so use dog language.
- You know dog language?
- A little bit.
[MIMICS GROWLING]
- [MIMICS GROWLING] Argh!
- [DOG BARKS]
What the hell are you doing?!
What on earth are you saying?!
Let me try, let me work
my charm on them.
[DOGS GROWLING]
Sit down.
[GROWLS]
- [SHRIEKS]
- Hey! Don't ever do that again!
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
- [KEYS JINGLE]
- [ENGINE TURNS OFF]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING,
THEN FADES]
- Right here, miss.
- Here?
- Hey, man.
- Yeah?
- What is this place? It's...
- What's up?
Hey, this looks
like a barracks--
She's looking for
motorcycle parts.
What are you going
to do to me?
We were going to give her
the bike that just came in.
Oh, is that so?
We'll clear her papers
so she can get it, man.
[MAN] Alright, bring her in.
Can't we just stay out here?
Hey, wait!
What are you doing?!
- Get inside!
- Get off me!
- I said get in!
- [SCREAMS] What are you doing?!
- Get in there!
- [GRUNTS LOUDLY]
Look where that got you!
[LAUGHS]
- You bastards! [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[SMACKS, KICK LANDS]
- [SCREAMING]
- [GRUNTING]
- Sit down!
- [BODY THUDS]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BARKING]
- Run!
- [DOGS BARKING]
- [CLAMORING]
[COMICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS TENSE]
Hey, who are you?
Uh, sir, I'm just looking
for my female companion.
She's wearing a red top
and pink shorts.
There's no woman here
with that description.
- You think you can run?!
- Just you try!
- [TEKLA SCREAMS] Help!
- Hold her down!
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
[BLOWS LANDING]
[TEKLA] Let me go!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [YELLING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- Hey!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTS, GROANING]
[ECHOING BLOW]
[THWACKS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[SLAMS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BODY SLAMMING]
[DOGS BARKING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
- Gabo!
- Tekla! Let's go!
[MEN GROANING]
Hey! Catch them!
Everyone, this way!
- Hurry!
- Come on!
[PANICKED SCREAMING]
Come closer, and I'll bite you!
You want that, huh?!
Catch them!
- Move!
- Out of the way!
Move!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Run! I'll distract them!
They're coming!
[TEKLA PANTING]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
He went that way! Hurry!
[MUD SQUELCHING]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
- Leave us alone!
- [DOGS BARKING]
Gabo! It's Gabo!
Gabo!
[WHISTLES]
[BARKING STOPS]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [DOGS BARKING]
Come on! Let's go!
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[PANTING]
Hurry! Come on!
- Faster!
- It's Tekla!
- Tekla!
- Let's bounce!
- Gabo's got his bike!
- Good! Let's scram!
- Which way's the exit?!
- This way!
- [DOGS BARKING]
- [MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
[SCREAMING]
[LOUD CRASH]
- Come on!
- Let's go!
- Run! Hurry!
- Move! Move!
Go! Go! Go!
- [MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARS]
- [DOGS BARKING]
- [MOTORCYCLE ENGINE ROARING]
- [THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Come on!
- Hurry!
- Faster!
- Move!
Run!
- [COUGHING]
- You good?
They didn't catch you?
Good thing we got away!
We were almost eaten by dogs!
That all?!
I almost got raped!
Good thing Gabo saved me.
- Huh?
- What?
I'm sorry you got
dragged into this.
But thank you so much
for your help.
Thanks to you,
I got this bike back.
Don't mention it, Gabo.
We promised we'd do everything
to help with
Mister Rudy's treatment.
We should go. I'll meet you
later at Ginintuang Lupa.
I'll drop by the hospital first
to check on Papa.
Alright. Take care, Gabo.
See you later.
You be careful too.
You better go
before they find you.
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
I have a mission for you.
Mr. Chan took the gold bars.
He'll be our key to proving
that Tiger is guilty.
I can't control
my daughter, Samantha.
You were a general.
Now, you can't even control
your low-ranked daughter?!
I'm sure they'll use Mr. Chan
to testify against Victor.
We have to make sure
he doesn't squeak.
[GUNSHOTS]
We need to get ahead
of our enemies.
You need to take the gold bars
from Mr. Chan.
I don't care if he dies
or not.
[GUNSHOTS]
- Let's go!
- Get inside!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Surround them!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
Umali will pay us
a huge sum.
I want you to do the job.
I'll take care of it.
- [THWACKS]
- [SCREAMS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- Mr. Chan!
[BLOWS LANDING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
- What's your name?
Gabo.
Your father doesn't have
much time left.
Doc! Help! Help!
- Gabo! What happened?!
- Papa!
- Papa! Papa!
- Code blue! Code blue!
Your father really can't
rely on you.
Doc, please do everything
to save my father!
Pa!
- [FLATLINES]
- Pa!